//add array of quiz questions


 const QUIZ = [
 {
 	question: "What is the name of Pawnee's prosperous neighboring town?",
 	answers: ['Eagleton', 'Haverford', 'Ludgate', 'Springfield'],
 	correctAnswer: 'Eagleton',
 },

 {
 	question: "What about Parks employee Jerry's personal life leaves his coworkers constantly baffled?",
 	answers: ['His entrepreneurial pursuits', 'His penchant for playing live jazz', 'His mastery of the Cones of Dunshire', 
 	'His beautiful wife and daughters'],
 	correctAnswer: 'His beautiful wife and daughters',
 },

{
 	question: "What is the name of Pawnee's highest elevation?",
 	answers: ['Sweetums Waste Lot', 'David Letterman Compost Bin', 'Larry Joe Bird Municipal Landfill', 
 	'Hoosier Hill'],
 	correctAnswer: 'Larry Joe Bird Municipal Landfill',
 },

{
 	question: "What is the name of Pawnee's lowest elevation?",
 	answers: ['Symth Hole', 'Badwater Basin', "Devil's Fissure", 'Wabash River Basin'],
 	correctAnswer: "Devil's Fissure",
 },

{
 	question: "What is Pawnee's number one, hottest club?",
 	answers: ["Pharoah's Dilemma", 'DUI', 'Snakehole Lounge', 'The Bulge'],
 	correctAnswer: 'Snakehole Lounge',
 },

{
 	question: "Name the breakout star of the Pawnee Harvest Festival?",
 	answers: ['Mouse Rat', "Li'l Sebastian", 'One Paw Papa', 'Just the Tip(Andy Dwyer Solo Project)'],
 	correctAnswer: "Li'l Sebastian",
 },

{
 	question: "Which woman in Ron's life is played by Park's actor Nick Offerman's actual wife, Megan Mullally?",
 	answers: ['Diane Lewis', 'Tammy 1', 'Tammy 2', 'Jane Callamezzo'],
 	correctAnswer: 'Tammy 2',
 },

{
 	question: 'Which Parks Department coworkers have a day of indulgence called "Treat Yo Self"?',
 	answers: ['Andy and Ron', 'Leslie and Ann', 'Tom and Donna', 'Donna and Jerry'],
 	correctAnswer: 'Tom and Donna',
 },

{
 	question: "Guest star Louis C.K. plays what character?",
 	answers: ['Bartender', 'Meat enthusiast', 'Police Officer', 'Animal Control Officer'],
 	correctAnswer: 'Police Officer',
 },

{
 	question: "Who is the largest employer in Pawnee?",
 	answers: ["Don's Cement", 'Sweetums Confectionary Corp', "Kernston's Rubber Nipples", "The Glitter Factory"],
 	correctAnswer: "Sweetums Confectionary Corp",
 }
]